Guide to the Acton Visual Materials at La Pietra MSS.LaPietra.001
Villa La Pietra
- Series II: Villa La Pietra
  - Subseries B: The Interior and the Collection
    - 5 Historic Albums mostly of the interior and works of art at present in the Collection or probably formerly once belonging to it.
      - Folder 1. Album labelled "1. Collezione Acton"
        - XXX. A.10.-1., undated; cuid5547 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 290)
          DIPINTO a tempera su tavola: Madonna in trono e angeli. h. 120 l. 59 Maestro del Bigallo (?), metà del XIII secolo. See also II.B.1.XXX. A.10.-1.15.-14. Photographed on an easel with a relief of the Madonna and Child and a bust of the Redeemer in the background.
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.LXV. D.12.-1.21.-31., undated; cuid5548 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 291)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LX. D.1.-1.20.-20., undated; cuid5549 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 292)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XLVIII. A.19.18.-45., undated; cuid5550 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 293)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXI. C.10.-2.14.-52., undated; cuid5551 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 294)
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.LVI. B.1.19.-73., undated; cuid5552 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 295)
          Photo by Brogi. Also in Historic Album II.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXX.-1.15.-1., undated; cuid5553 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 296)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII.-9.17.-9., undated; cuid5554 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 297)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII.-10.17.-10., undated; cuid5555 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 298)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XII.-21.12.-79., undated; cuid5556 (Box 26, Photo-album 1, Image 299)
      - Folder 2. Album labelled "2. Collezione Acton"
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.LXV. B.6.21.-26., undated; cuid5557 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 300)
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. C.11.-4.17.-57. (but with a capital in the background), undated; cuid5558 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 301)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XII. A.42.-1.12.-108., undated; cuid5559 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 302)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.IX. C.15.12.-44., undated; cuid5560 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 303)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.IX. C.1.12.-38., undated; cuid5561 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 304)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVI. C.1.-1.19.-76., undated; cuid5562 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 305)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. C.1.-4.17.-47., undated; cuid5563 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 306)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. C.1.-5.17.-48., undated; cuid5564 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 307)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. C.18.-5.17.-64., undated; cuid5565 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 308)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. C.18.-6.17.-65., undated; cuid5566 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 309)
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.LX. A.10.-1.20.-7., undated; cuid5567 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 310)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LX. A.10.-2.20.-8., undated; cuid5568 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 311)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XLVIII. D.20.-2.18.-91., undated; cuid5569 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 312)
          With the caption: "attribuita a Bonaventura Segna allievo di Duccio di Boninsegna".
        - XXX. B.16., undated; cuid5570 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 313)
          DIPINTO a tempera su tavola: Madonna col Bambino. h. 61,5 l. 39 Bernardo Daddi metà del XIV secolo. Annotated on the album page: "Pubblicato Vedi Tavola [1]93 Novembre 1935". See also II.B.1.XXX. B.16.-2.15.-36.
        - XXX. A.9., undated; cuid5571 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 314)
          DIPINTO a olio (?) su tavola: Madonna che adora il Bambino e un angelo. Nella cornice iscrizione: "Ave Maria Gratia Plena Dominus teco" e due stemmi: a tre gigli e rastrello nella parte superiore, sotto vaio rosso in campo blu tripartito con scacchiera, tre cerchi d'oro in campo rosso e fasce verticali blu e oro. h. 74 l. 63,5 Iacopo del Sellaio, seconda metà del XV secolo. See also II.B.1.XXX. A.9.15.-13.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LXXVI. D.3.-1.21.-49., undated; cuid5572 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 315)
          Also in Historic Album II. The label numbered 315. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Photos missing, replaced at an unknown date by photocopies of (duplicate) prints of the gardens of Villa La Pietra., undated; cuid5573 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 316.-347.)
        - Crucifix, undated; cuid5574 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 348)
          Detail, n. 349, is in IV.A.1.2.13.-1. The label numbered 348. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a Crucifix - detail of the torso of Christ in IV.A.1.2.13.-1., undated; cuid5575 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 349)
        - V. A.1., undated; cuid5576 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 350)
          DIPINTO a olio su tela con Martirio di S. Sebastiano, in cornice lignea scolpita e dorata (da villa Sassetti. h. 203 l. 137 Pittore veneto del XVII secolo.
        - Duplicate of II.B.4.25.-22., undated; cuid5577 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 351)
          The label numbered 351. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. A.19.-1.17.-37., undated; cuid5578 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 352)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. D.1.-1.17.-68., undated; cuid5579 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 353)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. D.10.17.-87., undated; cuid5580 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 354)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XIX. E.8.-3.13.-32., undated; cuid5581 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 355)
        - Duplicate of a garden gate in IV.A.7.11.39.-1.-2., undated; cuid5582 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 356)
          The label numbered 356. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a garden gate in IV.A.7. 11.39.-3.-4., undated; cuid5583 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 357)
          The label numbered 357. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a garden gate in IV.A.7. 11.39.-5.-6., undated; cuid5584 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 358)
          The label numbered 358. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. A.19.-4.17.-40., undated; cuid5585 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 359)
        - Duplicate of a fresco in Villa Natalia, II.C.3. 34.-121., undated; cuid5586 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 360)
          The label numbered 360. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a fresco in Villa Natalia, II.C.3. 34.-122., undated; cuid5587 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 361)
          The label numbered 361. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LXXVI. C.2.-2.21.-47., undated; cuid5588 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 362)
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-26., undated; cuid5589 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 363)
        - Duplicate of a landscape in IV.A.1., undated; cuid5590 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 364)
          In the same series as no. 363. The label numbered 364. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a landscape in IV.A.1., undated; cuid5591 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 365)
          In the same series as no. 363. The label numbered 365. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a chair in IV.A.10., undated; cuid5592 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 366)
          The label numbered 366. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVI. C.8.19.-78., undated; cuid5593 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 367)
          The label numbered 367. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of chairs in IV.A.10. 13.11.-1.-2., undated; cuid5594 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 368)
          The label numbered 368. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV. A.2.6-10.-1.-2., undated; cuid5595 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 369)
          The label numbered 369. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV. A.2.6.11.-1.-3., undated; cuid5596 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 370)
          The label numbered 370. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel in Villa Emilia II.C.2.34.-58., undated; cuid5597 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 371)
          The label numbered 371. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel in Villa Emilia II.C.2.34.-61., undated; cuid5598 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 372)
          The label numbered 372. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel in Villa Emilia II.C.2. 34.-60., undated; cuid5599 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 373)
          The label numbered 373. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-10., undated; cuid5600 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 374)
          Also in Historic Album IX.
          The label numbered 374. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-9., undated; cuid5601 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 375)
          The label numbered 375. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-12., undated; cuid5602 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 376)
          The label numbered 376. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-8., undated; cuid5603 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 377)
          The label numbered 377. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-11., undated; cuid5604 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 378)
          The label numbered 378. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.12.-1.-3., undated; cuid5605 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 379)
          The label numbered 379. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV.A.2. 6.13.-1.-2., undated; cuid5606 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 380)
          The label numbered 380. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.14.-1., undated; cuid5607 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 381)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LIII. A.30.19.-22., undated; cuid5608 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 382)
        - Near duplicate of II.B.1.LXII. A.2.20.-55., undated; cuid5609 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 383)
          The label numbered 383. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.7.38.-1.-3., undated; cuid5610 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 384)
          The label numbered 384. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.7.37.-1.-4., undated; cuid5611 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 385)
          The label numbered 385. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LXIV. C.2.21.-7., undated; cuid5612 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 386)
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.6.32.-2., undated; cuid5613 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 387)
          The label numbered 387. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.6.32.-6., undated; cuid5614 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 388)
          The label numbered 388. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.6.32.-1., undated; cuid5615 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 389)
          The label numbered 389. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.32.-3., undated; cuid5616 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 390)
          The label numbered 390. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.32.-7., undated; cuid5617 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 391)
          The label numbered 391. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.32.-5., undated; cuid5618 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 392)
          The label numbered 392. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of an oval painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.16.-1.-3., undated; cuid5619 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 393)
          The label numbered 393. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of an oval painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.15.-1.-3., undated; cuid5620 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 394)
          The label numbered 394. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.17.-1.-3., undated; cuid5621 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 395)
          The label numbered 395. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2. 6.18.-1., undated; cuid5622 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 396)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.6.34.-1.-2., undated; cuid5623 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 397)
          The label numbered 397. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with mythological scenes in IV.A.2.6.33.-1.-2., undated; cuid5624 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 398)
          The label numbered 398. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted screen (cupboard doors) in IV.A.2.7.20.-1.-9., undated; cuid5625 (Box 26, Photo-album 2, Image 399)
          The label numbered 399. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
      - Folder 3. Album labelled "3. Collezione Acton"
        - Duplicate of a painted screen (cupboard doors) in IV.A.2.7.20.-1.-9., undated; cuid5626 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 400)
          The label numbered 400. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted screen (cupboard doors) in IV.A.2.7.20.-1.-9., undated; cuid5627 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 401)
          The label numbered 401. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in IV.A.2.7.6.-1. with architectural elements and genre scenes, undated; cuid5628 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 402)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in IV.A.2.7.6.-2. with architectural elements and genre scenes, undated; cuid5629 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 403)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in IV.A.2.7.6.-3. with architectural elements and genre scenes, undated; cuid5630 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 404)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in IV.A.2.7.6.-4. with architectural elements and genre scenes, undated; cuid5631 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 405)
          The label numbered 405. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with architectural ruins in II.C.4.34.-182. (now in Villa Colletta), undated; cuid5632 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 406)
          The label numbered 406. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with architectural ruins in II.C.4.34.-181. (now in Villa Colletta), undated; cuid5633 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 407)
          The label numbered 407. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-26.a., undated; cuid5634 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 408)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XXXII. A.19.-4.17.-39., undated; cuid5635 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 409)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LX. A.4.-1.20.-5., undated; cuid5636 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 410)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LX. A.12.-1.20.-11., undated; cuid5637 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 411)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LIII. C.31.19.-38., undated; cuid5638 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 412)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-25., undated; cuid5639 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 413)
          The label numbered 413. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-24., undated; cuid5640 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 414)
          The label numbered 414. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.19.-1.-4., undated; cuid5641 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 415)
          The label numbered 415. not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.20.-1.-4., undated; cuid5642 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 416)
          The label numbered 416. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.21.-1.-4., undated; cuid5643 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 417)
          The label numbered 417. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.22.-1.-3., undated; cuid5644 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 418)
          The label numbered 418. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in II.C.4.34.-179. (now in Villa Colletta), undated; cuid5645 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 419)
          The label numbered 419. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in II.C.4.34.-178. (now in Villa Colletta), undated; cuid5646 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 420)
          The label numbered 420. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.23.-1.-5., undated; cuid5647 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 421)
          The label numbered 421. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with 'Chinoiserie' in II.C.4.34.-176. (now in Villa Colletta), undated; cuid5648 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 422)
          The label numbered 422. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.L. A.8.-2.19.-2., undated; cuid5649 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 423)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.L. A.8.-1.19.-1., undated; cuid5650 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 424)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XLVI. B.1.18.-7., undated; cuid5651 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 425)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVI. B.3.19.-75., undated; cuid5652 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 426)
        - Duplicate of a painted bedhead in IV.A.10. 13.36.-1.-2., undated; cuid5653 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 427)
        - Painted bedhead, undated; cuid5654 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 428)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.XX. B.2.-1.13.-92., undated; cuid5655 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 429)
          The label numbered 429. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a still life in II.C.5.35.-130. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5656 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 430)
        - Duplicate of a still life in II.C.5.35.-128. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5657 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 431)
          The label numbered 431. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a still life in II.C.5.35.-129. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5658 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 432)
          The label numbered 432. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a still life in II.C.5.35.-131. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5659 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 433)
          The label numbered 433. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.4.25.-25., undated; cuid5660 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 434)
          The label numbered 434. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.4.25.-26., undated; cuid5661 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 435)
          The label numbered 435. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.4.25.-24., undated; cuid5662 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 436)
          The label numbered 436. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.4.25.-23., undated; cuid5663 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 437)
          The label numbered 437. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LXXVI. C.5.21.-48., undated; cuid5664 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 438)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in II.C.5.35.-150. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5665 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 439)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in II.C.5.35.-151. (Villa Sassetti), undated; cuid5666 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 440)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-3., undated; cuid5667 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 441)
          The label numbered 441. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-1., undated; cuid5668 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 442)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-2., undated; cuid5669 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 443)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-5., undated; cuid5670 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 444)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-7., undated; cuid5671 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 445)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-6., undated; cuid5672 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 446)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.a.22.-4., undated; cuid5673 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 447)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.L. E.4.-2.19.-8., undated; cuid5674 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 448)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.L. E.4.-1.19.-7., undated; cuid5675 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 449)
        - Duplicate of painted screen in IV.A.2.7.17.-1.-3., undated; cuid5676 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 450)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LIII. D.4.19.-41., undated; cuid5677 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 451)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LIII.-1.19.-9., undated; cuid5678 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 452)
        - Duplicate photo of Villa La Pietra gardens missing and replaced at an unknown period by a photocopy, undated; cuid5679 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 453)
        - loose photo (possibly not originally here) of a duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.24.-1.-4., undated; cuid5680 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 454)
        - Duplicate of a painted panel with birds in IV.A.2.6.25.-1.-4., undated; cuid5681 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 455)
          The label numbered 455. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of two painted panels with birds in IV.A.2.6.26.-1.-4., undated; cuid5682 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 456)
          The label numbered 456. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in Chinese style in IV.A.2.7.21.-1.-3., undated; cuid5683 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 457)
          The label numbered 457. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in Chinese style in IV.A.2.7.22.-1.-3. (Villa Natalia?), undated; cuid5684 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 458)
          The label numbered 458. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVII. A.2.19.-81., undated; cuid5685 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 459)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVII. A.2.19-80., undated; cuid5686 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 460)
        - Duplicate of II.B.1.LVII. A.2.19.-82., undated; cuid5687 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 461)
        - Duplicate of a piece of painted furniture in oversize, IV.A.10. folder 286.-1., undated; cuid5688 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 462)
          The label numbered 462. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a detail of a piece of painted furniture in oversize, IV.A.2.7. folder 463., undated; cuid5689 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 463)
          The label numbered 463. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a piece of painted furniture in IV.A.10.13.38.-1.-2., undated; cuid5690 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 464)
          The label numbered 464. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in Chinese style in IV.A.2.7.23.-1.-3., undated; cuid5691 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 465)
          The label numbered 465. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in Chinese style in IV.A.2.7.23.-4.-6., undated; cuid5692 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 466)
          The label numbered 466. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel in Chinese style in IV.A.2. 7.24.-1.-3., undated; cuid5693 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 467)
          The label numbered 467. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.
        - Duplicate of a painted panel (with flowers) in IV.A.2.7.35.-1.-3., undated; cuid5694 (Box 26, Photo-album 3, Image 468)
          The label numbered 468. is not countersigned with a 'tick'.